<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RecipeList</string>
    <string name="procedure1">
        Procedure: \n
        Preheat oven to 200 C / Fan 180 C / Gas mark 5.
        Place the fish in an oven-proof dish and cover with the milk. Bake in the oven uncovered for 30 minutes or until the fish is cooked through.
        Peel and chop the potatoes, and boil with a pinch of salt until soft.
        When the fish is done drain the milk into a jug and put aside.
        Flake the fish with a fork and leave in the dish.
        Once potatoes are done, drain, then add 30g of the butter and a splash of the reserved milk and mash.
        In another saucepan melt the remaining 20g of butter on a medium heat and slowly add the flour stirring constantly until you get a smooth paste.
        Add the remaining milk a little bit at a time, stirring constantly, until you get a sauce-like consistency.
        Add the parsley and stir well. Cook for 5 minutes, constantly stirring.
        Add the sauce to the flaked fish and mix well. Top with the mashed potato and spread evenly.
        Sprinkle the grated cheese evenly over the potato topping.
        Place back in the oven for 30-40 minutes, or until the cheese is bubbling and slightly golden brown.
        Take out of the oven and leave to cool for 5 to 10 minutes.</string>
    <string name="recipe1">
        Recipe: \n
        500g white fish (haddock, cod, plaice, etc.) \n 600ml milk 6 to 8 \n large potatoes pinch salt 50g butter 1 1/2 \n tablespoons plain flour \n 2 tablespoons chopped parsley 100g grated cheese</string>
    <string name="procedure2">
        Procedure: \n
        1 Prep all of the salad ingredients and toss them together in a large bowl.
        2 Prepare the chicken salad dressing in a separate smaller bowl.
        Mix together the mayonnaise, preserves, and lemon juice.
        Taste for the proper balance of sweetness and acidity.
        The salad dressing should not be too sweet nor too sour.
        Add more preserves or lemon juice until you have reached the balance you want.
        Add salt and pepper to taste.
        3 Gently stir the dressing in with the chicken salad ingredients. Taste and add more salt and pepper if needed.</string>
    <string name="recipe2">
         Recipe: \n
        3/4 lb (2-3 cups) of cooked chicken meat*, coarsely chopped \n
2 stalks celery, chopped \n
1/2 red bell pepper, seeded and chopped \n
4-6 green olives, pitted and minced \n
1/4 cup of chopped red onion \n
1/2 to a whole apple, cored and  \n
1/3 head of iceberg head lettuce, sliced and choppped.</string>



    <string name="recipe3">
         Recipe: \n
        ½ lb. fresh flat miki noodles \n
10 ounces boneless chicken breast, sliced into thin pieces \n
1 Knorr Chicken Cube \n
½ medium cabbage, chopped \n
1 cup chopped carrots \n
½ cup chopped scallions \n
1 medium yellow onion, cubed \n
3 cloves garlic, crushed \n
1 tablespoon cornstarch \n
1 egg \n
6 to 7 cups water \n
1 teaspoon salt \n
¼ teaspoon ground black pepper \n
3 tablespoons cooking oil

    </string>

    <string name="procedure3">
        Procedure: \n
Heat oil in a cooking pot. \n
Saute garlic, onion, and carrots. \n
Add the sliced chicken. Cook until the chicken turns light brown.\n
Pour the water into the pot. Let boil.\n
Add Knorr chicken cube. Stir. Cover the pot. Cook the chicken between low to medium heat for 15 minutes.\n
Add cabbage and miki noodles. Cook for 8 to 10 minutes.\n
Add scallions. Stir.\n
Pour the egg. Continuously stir to prevent the egg from forming. \n
Add ¼ cup water to cornstarch and stir to mix. Pour it into the pot. Stir until the soup thickens. \n
Add salt and ground black pepper. Cook for 2 minutes. \n
Transfer to a serving bowl. Serve. \n
Share and enjoy!

    </string>
</resources>
